How many plastic carrier bags have you got in your house?
你家里有多少个塑料购物袋呢？
I seem to have cupboards full of them and it feels like they're taking over my home!
我的橱柜里似乎装满了它们，感觉它们都快占据我的家了！
The ubiquitous shopping bag is just one example of the million things we use made from this useful material, plastic.
这种无处不在的购物袋只是我们使用的由这种有用材料——塑料制成的无数物品中的一个例子。
But unfortunately, it's not the easiest thing to recycle and this is causing an environmental problem.
但不幸的是，塑料并不是最容易回收的东西，这正引发着一个环境问题。
Most of our everyday plastic items end up in landfill, left to rot away for many years.
我们日常使用的大多数塑料制品最终都被填埋在垃圾场，在那里腐烂多年。
But some of it blows away, blighting the countryside and causing damage to the natural environment and harming wildlife.
但其中一些会被风吹走，破坏乡村环境，对自然环境造成损害，并伤害野生动物。
The problem is most acute in our oceans.
这个问题在我们的海洋中最为严重。
Research has found an uninhabited island in the South Pacific is littered with the highest density of plastic waste anywhere in the world.
研究发现，南太平洋上一个无人居住的岛屿上，塑料垃圾的密度是世界上最高的。
Henderson Island, part of the UK‘s Pitcairn Islands group, has an estimated 37.7 million pieces of debris on its beaches.
亨德森岛是英国皮特凯恩群岛的一部分，据估计，它的海滩上有大约3770万件垃圾。
The study, published in the journal Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, described how remote islands act as a ’sink‘ for the world’s rubbish.
这项发表在《美国国家科学院院刊》上的研究描述了偏远岛屿是如何成为世界垃圾的“汇集地”的。
They become collecting points for fishing items and everyday things including toothbrushes, cigarette lighters and razors; things that we throw away.
它们成了渔具以及包括牙刷、打火机和剃须刀等日常用品的收集点，而这些都是我们扔掉的东西。
Dr Jennifer Lavers from the University of Tasmania says "Almost every island in the world and almost every species in the ocean is now being shown to be impacted one way or another by our waste."
塔斯马尼亚大学的詹妮弗·拉弗斯博士说：“现在看来，世界上几乎每一个岛屿，海洋里几乎每一个物种，都在以这样或那样的方式受到我们所产生的垃圾的影响。”
This highlights the potentially deadly effect of our disposable culture.
这凸显了我们的一次性文化潜在的致命影响。
When we throw something away, it doesn't just disappear, it goes somewhere and because of the durable nature of plastic, it takes a long time to decompose and stays there causing great damage to the ocean‘s ecology.
当我们扔掉某样东西时，它并不会凭空消失，它会去到某个地方。由于塑料的耐用性，它需要很长时间才能分解，并且会留在那里，对海洋生态造成巨大破坏。
Some other recent worldwide research estimates that 90% of all seabirds have swallowed plastic.
最近的一些其他全球研究估计，90%的海鸟都吞食过塑料。
And worse still, this plastic is broken down into tiny particles over a long period by the wind and the waves, then sea creatures at the bottom of the food chain ingest them.
更糟糕的是，这些塑料在长时间内会被风和海浪分解成微小的颗粒，然后食物链底层的海洋生物会吞食它们。
These creatures are eaten by the fish that we eventually consume.
而这些生物又会被我们最终食用的鱼吃掉。
The solution to this problem would be to use less plastic.
解决这个问题的办法是减少使用塑料。
Several countries now charge for using plastic carrier bags which reduces the amount used and some products now use natural and recyclable materials but it seems inevitable that plastic will continue to be necessary in many of the gadgets that we demand.
现在有几个国家对使用塑料购物袋收费，这减少了塑料的使用量，而且一些产品现在使用天然和可回收的材料。但似乎不可避免的是，在我们需要的许多小器具中，塑料仍然是必不可少的。
So next time you pick up a carrier bag, or buy a plastic bottle of water, spare a thought for the birds and animals on the remote Henderson Island.
所以，下次当你拿起一个购物袋，或者买一瓶塑料瓶装水的时候，想想偏远的亨德森岛上的鸟类和动物吧。
What do you do to help the environment?
你为保护环境做了些什么呢？